嘿，嘿，嘿。
Hey, hey, hey.
能把鼓声调大一点吗？
Can you turn the drum track up a bit?
是啊。
Yeah.
上啊，汤普森！
Let's go, Thompson!
- 加油，鲍比！ - 你能行的，你能行的！
- Go, Bobby! - You got it, you got it!
- 就是现在，伙计！ - 哇哦！
- This is it, man! - Whoa!
快上，快上！冲啊，冲啊，冲！快上去...-安全了！-噢！
Go, go! Go, go, go! Get on... - Safe! - Oh!
♪ 烈焰
♪ Fire
♪ 烈焰 ♪ 焚尽我所在的城邦 ♪ 焚尽你麾下儿郎 ♪ 焚尽高扬的旗帜 ♪ 焚尽谎言之书 ♪ 焚尽你的枪械与徽章
♪ Fire ♪ Set fire to the town I'm in ♪ Set fire to your boys and their kin ♪ Set fire to the flag held high ♪ Set fire to your book of lies ♪ Set fire to your gun and your badge
♪ 以烈火惩戒 ♪ 焚毁你虚伪的颂章 ♪ 焚尽你倚仗的权杖
♪ Set fire in reprimand ♪ Set fire to your nice review ♪ Set fire to the tools you use
♪ 火 ♪ 火 ♪
♪ Fire ♪ Fire ♪
这是最后通告！
This is last call!
-你们都还好吗，保罗？-很好，汉克。一切正常。
-You all good, Paul? -All good, Hank. All good.
谢谢，斯波。
Thanks, Spo.
汉克，你是最棒的。谢了，兄弟。
Hank, you're the best. Thanks, brother.
噢，别这样，伙计们。
Oh, come on, guys.
嗯哼！你们的人已经完蛋了。
Mm-mm-mm! Your boys are dead.
大都会队稳拿外卡了，老兄。
The Mets own the wild card, man.
我爱你，美铁，但恕我直言，滚一边去。
I love you, Amtrak, but with all due respect, fuck off.
汉克！别这样！
Hank! Come on!
嘿！你们几个，这里不能跳舞。
Hey! You guys, you can't dance in here.
胡说八道！
That's bullshit!
- 搞什么鬼？- 都怪朱利安尼。
- The fuck? - Blame Giuliani.
- 他说这是犯罪。- 去你的。
- He says it's a crime. - Fuck you.
你个混账东西。来跟我跳支该死的舞。
You motherfucker. Come fucking dance with me.
- 过来。咱们跳巴恰塔舞。- 放松点，老兄。
-Come here. Let's bachata. -Take it easy, buddy.
- 明白了。
- I got it.
好吧，这轮酒我请，然后你们就得走了。
All right, round of shots on me, then you gotta go.
-太棒了！ -好的。
-Fuck yeah! -All right.
-我给你准备了高级货。 -这些该死的追星小鬼。
-I got the good stuff for you. -Fucking teenyboppers.
- 嘿，汉克。- 干杯。
- Hey, Hank. - Salud.
你负责关店和存营业款没问题吧？
You cool closing up, doing the cash drop?
-嗯。-好的，那就这样。
-Mm-hm. -All right, then.
我们将在我的屋顶上读些诗，一起看日出。
We shall read some poetry and watch the sunrise from my rooftop.
- 没错！ - 那是 1975 年，卢让我去见安迪，但我当时不知道的是... 好了！有酒就干杯！
- Yes! - So, it was 1975 and Lou asked me to come see Andy, but what I didn't know was... All right! Drink 'em if you got 'em!
- 上面凉快吗，布里特？ - 嗯，我搞定了。
-Cool up here, Britt? -Yeah, I got it.
喂！
Yo!
这张脸我不太认得。
Not sure I recognize the face.
- 但他们看起来挺眼熟。 - 有品位。
-But they look familiar. -Classy.
是你自己露胸在先的。
You're the one flashing your tits.
今晚我救了个人 药物过量
I made a save tonight. OD.
太了不起了
That's incredible.
刚下班肾上腺素飙升 我脑子不太清醒
I got post-shift adrenaline. I'm not thinking clearly.
我们回你那儿吧，趁我头脑不清醒的时候。
Let's go back to your place, take advantage of my poor judgment.
我就指望你犯糊涂了。
I depend on your poor judgment.
我马上出来。
I'll be right out.
巨人队昨天得了 18 分。
The Giants scored 18 runs yesterday.
嗯哼。
Uh-huh.
-今天连 2 分都拿不到。-嗯哼。
-They couldn't score 2 today. -Mm-hm.
他们打成这样，怎么可能连扳三局？
How are they gonna make up three games playing like that?
你说的这些话一点魅力都没有。
Nothing you're saying is even a little bit sexy.
我不用说话就很有魅力。
I'm sexy without saying anything.
那你就给我闭嘴。
So then shut the fuck up.
孩子们，找个房间去亲热吧。
Come on, kids, get a room.
对不起，猫咪小姐。
I'm sorry, Miss Kitty.
-噢！-你没事吧？
-Oh! -You all right?
嘿！喂！你他妈的在干嘛呢，老兄？
Hey. Oi! What the fuck you doing, geezer?
哈哈，咱们这儿可有个活宝喜剧演员啊。
Haha. We've got a fucking comedian in the 'ouse.
你就这点本事？听着跟迪克·范戴克似的。
Is that the best you can do? You sound like Dick Van Dyke.
怎么样，伊冯？看起来不错嘛。
All right, Yvonne? Looking nice.
想约个小会是吧？
Little booty call, is it?
-你还是这么风趣，拉斯。-好吧，什么事？
-Charming as always, Russ. -All right. What's up?
没什么大事。我需要你帮我照看一下巴德。
Nothing's up. I need you to mind Bud for me.
-哇，不行。-必须行。
-Whoa, no. -Yes.
不行。我可不擅长照顾东西。
No. I am not good at taking care of things.
-布德是谁？-我的室友。
-Who's Bud? -My flatmate.
-他的猫。-我喜欢猫。
-His cat. -I like cats.
-很好。-它爱咬人。
-Good. -He's a biter.
它可从来没咬过你。它喜欢你。
He never fucking bit you. He loves you.
肯定还有别人。
There's gotta be someone else.
嘿，听着！别再只想着自己了！
Hey, listen! Stop thinking about yourself!
我爸中风了，对吧？
My dad had a stroke, yeah?
我得飞回伦敦。所以你只管喂他就行。
I've gotta fly back to London. So just feed him.
给他点爱之类的，对吧？
Give him a little love and that, right?
他就会高兴得不得了...他会很开心。
And he'll be fucking... He'll be 'appy.
伙计们。有点晚了。
Dudes. Kinda late.
-滚开，杜恩。-抱歉，杜恩。
-Fuck off, Duane. -Sorry, Duane.
我喜欢聚会，但有些人明天早上还要工作。
I like to party, but some of us work in the morning.
-滚开，杜安。-没问题，杜安。
-Fuck off, Duane. -Sure thing, Duane.
我又不是想报警什么的。
It's not like I wanna call the cops or anything.
嘿！带着你的华尔街工作和臭钱给我滚远点！
Hey! Fuck off with your Wall Street job and your fucking money and all!
- 我爸快不行了！——拉斯。
- My dad's dying 'ere! - Russ.
你这烂透了的混蛋！
You fucking rotten cunt!
没把你活剥了喂猫算你走运！
You're lucky I don't skin you alive and feed you to the fucking cat!
要知道，我可不是那种装腔作势的金融雅痞。
You know, I'm not some douchebag finance yuppie.
是的，你是！
Yes, you are!
我负责搭建网站。
I build websites.
这太酷了，杜安。
That is very cool, Duane.
晚安，伙计。
Good night, man.
你是想说早上好吧。
You mean good morning.
"我是做网站开发的。"
"I build websites."
嗯。你听到了吗？
Mm. Do you hear that?
- 嗯。 - 猫叫。
- Mm. - Cat.
你觉得杜安会报警抓他吗？
You think Duane'll call the cops on him?
真让人难过。我去看看他。
That's sad. I'm gonna go check on him.
- 好吧，快去快回。- 嗯。
-All right, well, hurry back. -Mm-hm.
- 邮箱一。- 您有一条新留言。
- Mailbox one. - You have one new message.
- 嗨。- 过来，小猫咪，小猫咪。
- Hi. - Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
亨利，是妈妈。
Henry, it's Mom.
唉，杰克又削减了我的工作时间。
Agh. Jack cut my hours back again.
我们的球员呢？
And our boys?
昨天还拿了 18 分，今天就一分未得？
Eighteen runs yesterday and zip-all today?
-确实如此。 -他们快把我逼疯了。
-Exactly. -They're making me crazy.
要是你在队里，咱们早锁定外卡赛资格了。
They'd have the wild card locked if you were on the team.
给我打电话。爱你。
Call me. Love you.
巨人队加油！
Go Giants!
- 爱你，妈妈。
- Love you, Mom.
- 哇！猫！- 猫跑出来了！
- Ooh! Cat! - Cat on the loose!
哦！他在这里面。
Oh! He's in here.
你怎么了？
What's wrong with you?
--嘿。
--Hey.
哦，不。等一下。不行！
Oh, no. Wait a minute. No!
-宝贝，他不会留在这里的。-哦，拜托。
-Baby, he's not staying here. -Oh, come on.
他会把毛发弄得到处都是。
He's gonna get hair all over the bed.
看！
Look!
他是爱你的。
He loves you.
我喜欢狗。小时候我们家就养过狗。
I like dogs. We had dogs growing up.
当然了。你喜欢狗和棒球……你会给妈妈打电话，有钱了就寄钱给她……真是个善良的小镇男孩。
Of course you did. You like dogs and baseball... You call your mom, send her money when you can... Such a nice small-town boy.
小镇男孩，是吧？
Small-town boy, huh?
我可没那么善良。
I'm not so nice.
哦，是吗？
Oh, yeah?
噢。
Ooh.
小心你手里的家伙指哪儿。
Better watch where you point that thing.
-你是个坏小子吗？-试试看啊。
-You a bad boy? -Try me.
我该害怕吗？
Should I be scared?
你们这些城里姑娘以为自己很厉害，是吧？
You city girls think you're so tough, huh?
是的，我们相当快。
Yeah, we're pretty fast.
-有多快？-比你快。
-How fast? -Faster than you.
哦，是吗？
Oh, yeah?
那可是上好的啤酒。
That's a perfectly good beer.
-那就待会儿喝。-嗯。
-So drink it after. -Mm.
你还好吗？
You OK?
我没事。
Yeah, I'm fine.
好的。
OK.
-冠军的早餐。  -没错。
-Breakfast of champions. -Yep.
比那些发霉的冷冻贝果强多了。
Better than those moldy frozen bagels.
好的。
All right.
-你要走了？  -是啊，都快 1 点了。
-You gotta go? -Yeah, it's almost 1:00.
-你确定没事？  -嗯，一切都好。
-Sure you're OK? -Yeah. All good.
好的。
All right.
牙膏用完了。
You're out of toothpaste.
-待会打给你？ -你有我号码。
-Call you later? -You got my number.
巨人队正对阵海盗队。
And the Giants are facing the Buccos.
但他们落后三场且只剩七场比赛可打。
But they're three games back with only seven to play.
巨人队完了！拿叉子来！我的叉子在哪？
The Giants are cooked! Get a fork! Where is my fork?
你要叉子？我给你把叉子，你这混... 嘿，老兄。这不是给你的。
You want a fork? I got a fork for you, you f... Hey, Bud. It's not for you.
那是人类的食物。
That's human food.
行吗？
All right?
什么？
What?
哦，你饿了。
Oh, you're hungry.
好的，没问题。我去给你弄点吃的。
Yeah, all right. I'll go get you some food.
喂！你是谁？
Hey! Who are you?
拉斯在家吗？
Is Russ home?
你是谁？
Who are you?
哦。大块头。
Oh. Big boy.
棒球先生
Mr. Baseball.
♪ 用一场球赛终结他 ♪
♪ Take him out with a ball game ♪
-哇哦，哇哦。嘿。-拉斯在里面吗？
-Whoa, whoa. Hey. -Is Russ in there?
-不，他不在。-嗯。
-No, he's not here. -Mm.
♪ 骗子骗子 ♪ 火烧裤子 ♪
♪ Liar, liar ♪ Pants on fire ♪
那么...拉斯在哪？
So...where's Russ?
呃...这不关你的事。
Uh... It's none of your business.
-让我过去。-小心那个面包圈，老兄。
-Let me by. -Watch the bagel, man.
啊，好的，好的，棒球先生。
Ah, OK, OK, Mr. Baseball.
开球。
Play ball.
-老兄，住手！这样太过分了！-管好你自己的事！
-Dude, stop! That's not cool! -Mind your fucking business!
报警，杜安！
Call the cops, Duane!
没错！快住手，不然我就报警了！
Yeah! Stop or I'll call the cops!
不，杜安，快报警！
No, actually call the cops, Duane!
我在打了！
I'm calling!
他们走了吗？
Are they gone?
嘿，老兄。
Hey, Bud.
这可不太妙。
That's not good.
你看到辛迪因为丹维尔那事气炸了吗？
You clock Cindy with that burnout from Danville?
是啊。
Yeah.
梅丽莎说她是故意跟他好来气你的。
Melissa said she got with him to piss you off.
哥们，辛迪爱干嘛干嘛。
Man, Cindy can do what she wants.
是啊，当然。
Yeah, right.
不过说真的
But for real, though.
看到看台上那个道奇队的球探了吗？
You see that Dodgers scout in the stands?
你干嘛老针对我？今天怎么回事？
Why are you riding me? What is this today?
-他对你有意思！-道奇队拿到了第二顺位选秀权
-He was into you! -Dodgers got the second pick.
-我不会那么高调的。-但万一...？
-I won't go that high. -But what if...?
不，我才不会被道奇队选中呢。
No, I'm not getting drafted by the Dodgers.
第 15 顺位。那就是我。
15th pick. That's me.
在大联盟选秀第 15 顺位，旧金山巨人队选择：
With the 15th pick of the Major League draft, the San Francisco Giants select:
汉克·汤普森！
Hank Thompson!
这才像话嘛。
That's what I'm talking about.
♪ 那就给她几寸... ♪
♪ So give her inches... ♪
- 还要再来一杯吗？- 这还用问？
-You want another one? -You have to ask?
好吧，既然你不介意，老兄，辛迪当时可真迷人。
Well, then, if it doesn't bother you, man, Cindy was looking fine.
靠！
Oh, shit!
该死，该死！
Shit, shit!
-♪ 我在这儿... ♪ -汉克！
-♪ Here I am... ♪ -Hank!
♪ 像飓风一样摇摆你 ♪
♪ Rock you like a ♪
嘿。嘘。没事的。
Hey. Shh. It's OK.
-嗯。 -没事的。
-Mm. -It's OK.
哦。什么...？
Oh. What...?
别紧张。放松点。
Take it easy. Take it easy.
他们在你身上开了个洞。取走了一颗肾。
They cut a hole in you. They took a kidney out.
什么？他们为什么这么做？
What? Why'd they do that?
血管破裂了，它会要了你的命。
It was ruptured and it was gonna kill you.
别看。就... 好吧。
Don't look. Just... OK.
我已经...多久了？
How long have I...?
你已经昏迷了两天。
You've been in and out of it for two days.
-两天？
-是啊。
-Two days? -Yeah.
-天啊。
-发生什么了？
-Oh, shit. -What happened?
噢，我妈呀。
Oh, my mom.
有电话吗？你带手机了吗？
Is there a phone? Do you have your phone?
-有。有。-我能...？
-Yeah. Yeah. -Can I...?
两天没接到电话了。
Two days without a call.
嘿，妈妈，是我。
Hey, Mom, it's me.
不，我没事。抱歉，我只是...之前生病了。
Yeah, no, I'm fine. I'm sorry. I just... I was sick.
嗯，就是食物中毒。
Yeah, it was just food poisoning.
不过别担心，我现在好多了。有个朋友陪着我。
But, hey, I'm OK. I got a friend with me.
不是那种关系，就是普通朋友。
No, just a friend.
嘿。我前几天真是昏昏沉沉的。
Hey. I was really out of it the last couple days.
那个...后来怎么样了？
What happened with the...?
真的吗？
Really?
哦，哇，太好了...哎哟。
Oh, wow, that's great... Ow.
呃...嘿，我现在有点迷糊，所以...呃...我们能...？
Um... Hey, I'm really out of it, so... Um... Can we...?
好的，嗯。我爱你。巨人队加油。
All right, yeah. I love you. Go Giants.
巨人队只落后一场比赛了。
Giants are only one game back.
你的优先事项真让我着迷。
Your priorities fascinate me.
-我让你着迷。-我可没这么说。
-I fascinate you. -Not what I said.
啊，你在我床边呢。
Aw, here you are at my bedside.
-我刚到。-嗯哼。
-I just got here. -Uh-huh.
嗯哼。哦，刚才有个警察来过了。
Mm-hm. Oh, a cop came by.
我不知道该跟她说什么。
I didn't know what to tell her.
她留下了名片。
She left her card.
到底发生什么了？
What the hell happened?
几个家伙来找拉斯，不知为何对我发火。
Some guys, they came looking for Russ, and they got pissed at me for some reason.
拉斯。果然是他。
Russ. Of course.
我得离开这儿。
I have to get out of here.
你刚做完手术。
You just had surgery.
不行，我付不起这个。得趁账单还没滚得更大之前离开。
No, I can't afford this. I gotta get out before I rack up a bigger bill.
——好吧，行。
--Yeah, OK.
可以。但有规矩要遵守。
Fine. But there are rules.
-“低钠”。-我不喜欢盐。
-"Low sodium". -I don't like salt.
-“禁止吸烟”。-吸烟很恶心。
-"No smoking". -Smoking is gross.
-“不含咖啡因”。-咖啡因让我紧张不安。
-"No caffeine". -Caffeine makes me jittery.
还有，呃...“禁止饮酒”。
And, um... "No alcohol".
永远。
Forever.
好的。
OK.
说真的，汉克。肾脏是用来处理毒素的。
Seriously, Hank. Kidneys process toxins.
酒精就是毒素，明白吗？
Alcohol is a toxin, do you understand?
是啊。
Yeah.
什么？我喝得又不多。
What? I don't drink that much.
好的。
OK.
给你，兄弟。
Here you go, Bud.
话说你好几天没联系我了，没事吧？
Anyway, you haven't called me for days. Are you OK?
给我打电话。爱你。巨人队加油。
Call me. Love you. Go Giants.
悠着点，硬汉。
You have to take it easy, tough guy.
我喜欢有备无患，以防需要招待客人。
I like to be prepared in case I have to entertain.
我不喜欢蠢男人，汉克。
I don't like stupid guys, Hank.
如果你想要找个银行家之类的，杜安就在走廊那头。
Well, if you want a banker or something, Duane's right down the hall.
这一点都不好笑。他又不是银行家。
That's not funny. He's not a banker.
他搭建网站。
He builds websites.
-你怎么回事？ -什么？你什么意思？
-What is it with you? -What? What do you mean?
每次遇到正经事就故意装傻。
Purposely acting stupid whenever shit gets real.
我才没有。
I don't do that.
好的。我来处理。
OK. I do that.
但我真的不知道你想要什么。
But I really don't know what you want.
我想知道这事能不能当真。
I wanna know if I can take this seriously.
你...？你想认真对待？
You...? You wanna get serious?
我们就在那个地方。
We're at that place.
要么继续深入，要么... ...就此退出。
Either we go deeper or... ...we get out.
好吧。那么... 怎样才能让你认真对待我们？
OK. So... What do you need to take us seriously?
我只需要确认你是个能搞定自己烂摊子的人。
I just need to know that you're a guy that can take care of his shit.
我不想和一个逃避自己生活的人在一起。
I don't wanna be with someone who's running away from his life.
你越是逃避恐惧的东西，就越会被它控制。
You run away from what you're afraid of, then it owns you.
-待会打给你？ -你有我号码。
-Call you later? -You got my number.
你拿了我的帽子。
You got my hat.
怎么？你以为我不敢动手？
What? You don't think I'll do it?
去你的。
Fuck you.
--你有毛病啊？走开。
--What's your problem? Shoo.
别在床上。嘿，下来。
Not on the bed. Hey, get down.
哥们，别这样！
Bud, come on!
老兄。
Dude.
我有喜欢狗的理由。
There are reasons I like dogs.
喂，杰森！垃圾还没收走吗？
Yo, Jason! Still no trash pickup?
对我来说没问题！
Works out OK for me!
嘿，你那里面有罐子吗？
Hey, you got any cans in there?
哦，不，老兄。只有瓶子。
Oh, no, man. Just bottles.
喝几罐高杯啤酒。帮兄弟个忙。
Drink a couple tallboys. Help a brother out.
我的错。给。
My bad. Here.
嘿，你人不错啊，哈利。
Hey, you're all right, Harry.
...他的保镖阿尔和约瑟夫。
...his bodyguards Al and Joseph.
杰瑞！杰瑞！杰瑞！杰瑞！
Jerry! Jerry! Jerry! Jerry!
哦，该死。
Oh, shit.
从这该死的床上滚下去！
Off the fuckin' bed!
哦，该死。
Oh, shit.
靠。
Shit.
嗯哼。你看到几个？
Mm-hm. How many did you see?
呃，总共三个吧，我想。
Uh, three altogether, I think.
罗曼警官？
Detective Roman?
介意我用下洗手间吗？
You mind if I use the facilities?
犯罪现场禁止随地大小便。
We're not allowed to crap at a crime scene.
好的。
OK.
按住把手不放，否则会堵塞。
Hold the handle down or it clogs.
我知道怎么冲厕所。
I know how to flush a toilet.
警察工作最光鲜的时刻。
Police work at its most glamorous.
哎呀。嘿。
Aw. Hey.
看看那个。
Look at that.
嘿，小猫咪。
Hey, kitty.
-它会咬人。我不建议... -嘿。
-He's a biter. I wouldn't... -Hey.
--噢！哦！
--Ooh! Oh!
-这该死的咬人狂。-是啊，抱歉。
-Fuckin' man-eater. -Yeah, I'm sorry.
你觉得你看到了三个人。能描述一下其中任何一个吗？
So you think you saw three. Can you describe any of 'em?
呃，有前两天打我的那两个乌克兰人，然后...你怎么知道他们是乌克兰人？
Well, there were the two Ukrainians who beat me up the other day, and then... How do you know they're Ukrainian?
他们有口音，而且小乌克兰区就在附近。
They had accents, and Little Ukraine's right around the corner.
不，不对，他们不是乌克兰人。
Yeah, no, they're not Ukrainian.
黑手党多年前就接管了那个街区。
The mafia took over that neighborhood years ago.
-他们听起来不像意大利人。-是俄罗斯黑帮。
-They didn't sound Italian. -Russian mafia.
比意大利黑手党更暴力。
More violent than the Italians.
-食物更难吃。-好吧，真棒。
-Worse food. -Well, great.
你是粉丝吗？还是玩过？
Hey, you a fan? Or you played?
玩过。
I played.
嗯。大学？半职业？
Hm. College? Semi-pro?
呃，高中。
Uh, high school.
哦，还以为你打过真正的篮球呢。
Oh. Thought maybe you played real ball.
我打过真正的篮球。
I played real ball.
嗯哼。
Uh-huh.
你对迈纳先生的犯罪活动了解多少？
What do you know about Mr. Miner's criminal activities?
一无所知。拉斯？他不是罪犯。
Nothing. Russ? He's not a criminal.
汤普森先生，您在这里住了多久？
How long you been here, Mr. Thompson?
哦，在纽约待了 11 年，这个地方住了六七年吧。
Well, 11 years in New York and six, seven in this place.
嗯哼，时间够长，足以目睹所有的变化。
Mm-hm. Long enough to see all the changes.
警力增加了，高档餐厅也多了。
Increased policing. Fancy restaurants.
-高档化。-没错。
-Gentrification. -Yeah.
但即便有这么多变化，缉毒队的警探也不会为了一起胡扯的袭击抢劫案出现在这里。
But even with all those changes, you don't get a detective from Narcotics here on a bullshit assault and robbery.
-缉毒队？-我来是因为拉斯·迈纳，他在一起正经的毒品调查案中是重要嫌疑人。
-Narcotics? -I'm here 'cause Russ Miner, he's a person of interest in a non-bullshit narcotics investigation.
他跟你提过这事吗？
He talk to you about that?
不，他只是说要去伦敦见他父亲。
No. He just said he had to go see his dad in London.
你从拉斯那里买毒品？
You buy your drugs from Russ?
我不吸毒。
I don't do drugs.
-几乎不吸。-你和他一起贩毒？
-Hardly ever. -You deal drugs with him?
不，女士。
No, ma'am.
你上次和这些人说话是什么时候？
When was the last time you talked to these guys?
不知道。
I don't know.
我不认识那些人。
I don't know those guys.
就这几个家伙？他们可是可怕的怪物。
These guys right here? They're scary monsters.
不管你和他们有什么勾当，最好在他们决定剜掉你眼睛之前告诉我。
Whatever you're doing with them, you should tell me about it before they decide you'd look better with your eyes cut out.
我和他们毫无瓜葛。
I'm not doing anything with them.
听懂了吗？我...我...
OK? I... I...
你他妈在耍我？
Are you messing with me?
--我就是在耍你。
--I'm kinda fucking with you.
永远猜不到会出什么岔子。
Never know what'll pop loose.
我按住了，但它还是堵了。
I held it down but it clogged anyway.
-我在走廊那头完工了。-你非要把这位市民的管道搞砸了才告诉我？
-I'm done across the hall. -You couldn't tell me that before you ruined this citizen's plumbing?
-我得走了。-赶紧给我滚。
-I had to go. -Get the fuck outta here.
好吧，我直接问你个问题。
All right, I'mma ask you a direct question.
-行。-你他妈在耍我吗？
-OK. -Are you fucking with me?
没有。我什么都不知道。我没什么可耍的。
No. I don't know anything. I've got nothing to fuck with.
什么？
What?
我又在耍你了。
I'm fucking with you again.
永远猜不到会冒出什么幺蛾子。
Never know what'll pop loose.
但经验告诉我你有所隐瞒。
But experience tells me you're not telling me something.
你觉得那是无关紧要的事。
You think it's something that doesn't matter.
但也许会的。所以再来一次：
But it might. So one more time:
你有什么想告诉我的吗？
Is there anything you wanna tell me?
呃...我真的好害怕。
Uh... I'm really scared.
-他们不在乎你。-他们把我送进了医院。
-They don't care about you. -They put me in the hospital.
那只是...附带伤害。
That's...collateral damage.
你没什么好担心的。
You have nothing to worry about.
除非那些可怕的怪物出现。
Unless the scary monsters come around.
你看到它们的话，就叫我。
You see them, you call me.
-还好吗？ -还好。
-All right? -All right.
今天你的小伙子们表现如何？
How'd your boys do today?
他们打败了海盗队，所以还落后一场。
They beat the Pirates, so one game back.
我押大都会队赢。
My money's on the Mets.
汤普森先生，您好。
Good day, Mr. Thompson.
好了，各位，我们走吧。
OK, fellas, let’s go.
哦，该死。
Oh, fuck.
搞什么鬼，巴德？
What the fuck, Bud?
你吃了什么？
What did you eat?
有什么区别呢？
What's the difference?
她说这些杏仁味道更苦一些。
She said they're a little more bitter.
- 那你猜我会怎么说？- 怎么说？
-Well, you know what I say. -What?
- 如果它嘎嘎叫...- 没错。
- If it quacks... - Exactly.
这正是我想说的。它就是颗杏仁。
That was my point. It's an almond.
罗斯？
Russ?
有人吗？
Hello?
你在干嘛？我车停路边挡道了。
What are you doing? I'm double-parked.
罗曼警探，纽约警局的。
Detective Roman, NYPD.
留言必回。
Leave a message, call you back.
我是汉克·汤普森。
It's Hank Thompson.
那个...那些可怕的怪物刚才就在这里。
The, uh... The scary monsters were just here.
我觉得我可能发现了重要线索，快给我打电话或者...不行，这里不安全。
And I think I may have found something important, so just call me or... No. I don't think it's safe here.
我稍后给你回电话。
I'll call you back.
嘿，好久不见。
Hey. Long time no see.
你记下撞你那辆卡车的车牌号了吗？
You got the license of that truck that hit you?
- 去你的，老兄。 - 嘿，老兄，你没事吧？
-Screw you, man. -Hey, man, you OK?
嘿，保罗！保罗！保罗！
Hey, Paul! Paul! Paul!
哇！伦诺克斯·刘易斯到场了，伙计！
Oh! Lennox Lewis is in the house, man!
-来，喝一杯，冠军。 -不行，我不能喝。我有事相求。
-Here, have a drink, champ. -No, I can't. I need a favor.
-操，别提什么帮忙！见鬼。 -不行，我真的不能喝，兄弟。
-Oh, fuck favors! Fuck. -No, I can't drink, man.
好吧好吧，那就算了。行。
All right, all right, then. OK.
那就为巨人队干杯吧。好吗？
Then here's a toast to the Giants. OK?
巨人！巨人！巨人！
Giants! Giants! Giants!
别诋毁你最喜欢的球队啊，伙计。
Don't diss your favorite team, man.
你还等什么？一口气干了。
What are you waiting for? Chugalug.
-好吧，就一个！ -巨人！巨人！
-All right, just one! -Giants! Giants!
-认真的吗。 -巨人！
-Seriously. -Giants!
♪ 我是个贱人，也是个情人 ♪ 我是个孩子，也是个母亲 ♪ 我是个罪人，我是个... ♪
♪ I'm a bitch, I'm a lover ♪ I'm a child, I'm a mother ♪ I'm a sinner, I'm a... ♪
罗斯，你他妈把我卷进什么鬼事了，老兄？
Russ, what the fuck did you get me into, man?
可怕的怪物和超级怪人。
Scary monsters and super creeps.
嘿！嘿，我们来喝几杯？
Hey! Hey, we taking shots?
嘿，收到留言后给我回电话，兄弟。
Hey, you call me back when you get this, man.
布里特！
Britt!
嘿，老板，再来杯啤酒。
Hey, barkeep, another brew here.
滚开。
Fuck off.
好吧，没问题。
Well, all right.
自助服务，这就来。
Self-service, here we go.
♪ 当巨人来到小镇时 ♪
♪ When the Giants come to town ♪
让他滚出去。
Get him the fuck outta here.
不想再给他来一杯吗？
Don't wanna get him another drink?
嘿，我们就是找点乐子。
Hey, we were just having some fun.
哦，保罗你他妈能不能成熟点！
Oh, grow the fuck up, Paul!
--小心！
--Watch out!
三垒跑者冲向本垒！
Runner on third, he breaks for home!
胜负难分！他安全上垒！
It's gonna be close! He is safe!
-观众瞬间沸腾！-快他妈让开！
-And the crowd goes wild! -Out of the fucking way!
本垒在这边，大明星。
Home base is this way, superstar.
超级巨星。
Superstar.
来吧，宝贝，别在街上待着。
Come on, baby. Get out of the street.
我们送你回家吧。
Let's get you home.
什么？
What?
你觉得这很好笑吗？
You think that's funny.
你想让我直面恐惧，却觉得这很好笑。
You want me to face my fears, but you think that's funny.
什么？
What?
你到底想说什么？
What is it you're trying to say?
我曾拥有那么多。
I had so much.
明明就在这里。然后...好吧。
It was right here. And then... OK.
那你告诉我，我该怎么面对这一切？
So you tell me, how do I face that?
你明白吗？曾经拥有一切如今只剩垃圾——这让我如何自处？
You know, how do I face when I had so much and now all I have is garbage?
-垃圾？说得好。-不，亲爱的。
-Garbage? Nice. -No. Baby.
-出租车！-我不是说你。
-Taxi! -I didn't mean you.
今晚我不用再看孩子了。
Yeah, I'm done babysitting tonight.
别这样嘛，宝贝。
Come on, baby.
嗨。唐人街？
Hi. Chinatown?
哈利，我的孩子。
Harry, my boy.
哦，该死。
Oh, fuck.
♪ 我得走了 表演时间到了♪ 我来了... ♪
♪ I've got to leave It's time for a show ♪ Here I am... ♪
- 汉克！- ♪ 像摇滚一样摇摆... ♪
- Hank! - ♪ Rock you like a... ♪
戴尔。
Dale.
他醒了。
He's awake.
懒人沙发。
La-Z-Boy.
唐恩都乐甜甜圈。
Dunkin' Donuts.
起床啦，太阳晒屁股了。
Rise and shine.
你对那只猫做了什么？
What'd you do to the cat?
我摸了摸那只臭猫。
I pet the shitty cat.
然后它咬了我。所以... ...我就踢了那只臭猫。
And it bit me. So... ... I kicked the shitty cat.
不，不，不，不，不，不，不。我们是来跟那家伙谈话的。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. We here to talk to the guy.
好的，好的，好的。
OK, OK, OK.
-给他拴上狗链 -抱歉
-Put him on a leash. -Sorry.
听着，汉克...
Mira, Hank...
让我来解释一下情况。
Let me explain what's happening.
这些家伙，他们想打到你开口为止。
These guys, they wanna hit you until you tell them things.
但我相信肯定有更好的方式能达成理解。
But I believe that there has to be a better way to come to an understanding.
La pistola.（西班牙语：手枪）
La pistola.
有些人挥舞着枪，就像在炫耀他们那玩意儿似的。
Some guys wave a gun around like it's their... ...dick.
但我可不需要挥舞什么东西来示威。
But I don't need to wave anything around.
要么得到我想要的，要么就让我的枪替我说话。
Either I get what I want or my pistol talk for me.
明白吗？
You understand?
拉斯去伦敦见他老爸了。
Russ went to see his dad in London.
完美。
Perfecto.
但他先给了你什么东西，对吧？
But first he gave you something, right?
是啊。
Yeah.
哦，对。有一把钥匙。不过不是他直接给我的，而是藏在...猫砂盆里。
Oh, yeah. There was a key. Well, he didn't give it to me, but he hid it in the... the litter box.
-在卫生间。-全程没挨打。
-It's in the bathroom. -All with no hitting.
全垒打，棒球先生。
Home run, Mr. Baseball.
它藏在一坨假橡胶便便里。
It was in a fake rubber poo.
嗯...我就是在那儿找到的。
Um... That's where I found it.
听着，我当时醉得厉害，完全不记得发生了什么。但我洗了床单，然后杰森...假便便。
Look, I got so wasted I don't remember what happened, but I washed the sheets and then Jason... Fake poo.
真是搞笑。但没有钥匙。
So funny. But no key.
他不懂什么叫善意。
He doesn't understand nice.
嗯。
Hm.
-看我找到了什么。-该你出手了。
-Look what I found. -Do your thing.
-停下。快停下。-该你了。
-Stop. Just stop. -Your turn.
停下。求你快停下。让我想一下。
Stop. Please just stop. Let me think for a second.
我真是喝高...
I got really dru...
不，住手！
No, stop!
-钥匙在哪儿？-等等 等等 先别急
-Where is the key? -Wait, wait, wait. Just wait.
啊！该死！
Ah! Fuck!
♪ 用一场棒球赛把他搞定... ♪
♪ Take him out with a ballgame... ♪
-钥匙能开什么？ -我不知道！
-What does the key open? -I don't know!
-嗯？ -我不知道！
-Huh? -I don't know!
我不知道！
I don't know!
♪ 给我买啤酒、坚果和饼干，杰克... ♪
♪ Buy me beer, nuts and crackers, Jack... ♪
听着，我喝醉了！我断片了！
Listen, I got drunk! I blacked out!
我不记得自己干了什么！
I don't remember what I did!
伙计们，你们在干什么我都听得见！
Dudes, I can hear whatever you're doing!
-那王八蛋是谁？-就那个雅痞混蛋。
-Who the fuck is that? -It's the yuppie asshole.
让他滚蛋。
Tell him to fuck off.
现在。
Now.
-嘿，滚远点，杜安。-老兄。
- Hey, fuck off, Duane. - Dude.
认真的。赶紧滚，伙计！
Seriously. Fuck off, man!
嘿，老兄，你他妈能滚远点吗？
Hey, dude, how about you fuck off?
- 认真的？ - 不不不不！
- Seriously? - No, no, no, no!
滚蛋，杜安！
Fuck off, Duane!
你他妈在干嘛？
The fuck are you doin'?
-...控制住他。-抱歉。
-...to control him. -Sorry.
那个雅皮士会报警的。快走。
The yuppie will call the police. Come on.
我们知道你和那个女警谈过了。
We know that you talked to the lady cop.
要是你再联系那个婊子，或者任何警察，我们就杀光你在乎的每一个人。
If you call that bitch again, or any cop, we will kill everyone you care about in the whole world.
我的号码。
Mi número.
拿钥匙，打给我。别瞎搞。
Get the key, call me. Don't fuck around.
球赛。
Ball game.
我要去迪士尼乐园。
I'm going to Disneyland.
好的，冷静点！
OK, all right. Chill!
我没法照顾他了。
I couldn't take care of him.
天呐。
Holy shit.
-他们伤害了他。-别这样。
-They hurt him. -Come on.
嘿，兄弟。
Hey, Buddy.
你这状态可真够猛啊，汉克。
You're on a real fucking roll, Hank.
说真的，这他妈太牛逼了。
Seriously, that shit's impressive.
呃...
Uh...
-聪明。 -咱俩得少混一起了。
-Clever. -We gotta stop hanging out.
咱俩的脑回路都同步了。
Our cycles are syncing up.
--可爱。
--Cute.
好的，我们来看看这个。
All right, let's check this out.
还行，不算太糟。
All right, not too bad.
只是掉了几个订书钉，应该没问题。
Just lost a few staples. Should be OK.
-你在干什么？-我在叫辆巴士。
-What are you doing? -I'm calling a bus.
不行，你不准联系任何人。
No, you can't call anyone.
你得把那个伤口缝合好。
You have to get that closed up.
- 你来弄。
- You do it.
-我不是医生 -我不能去医院 也不能去任何可能招来警察的地方
-I'm not a doctor. -I can't go to the hospital or anything that might involve cops.
谁把你弄成这样？到底发生了什么？
Who did this to you? What's going on?
缝上就行 我没事的
Stitch it up. I'll be OK.
我这里没有缝合线 我没有...我做不到
I don't have sutures here. I don't have... I can't.
好了好了，我有主意了。
All right, all right. I have something.
不过会留下难看的疤痕。
It's gonna leave a nasty scar, though.
别动。必须固定住。
Stop moving. It has to set.
别动。
Stay still.
好了。就像前线处理的那样。
OK. Just like they do it on the front lines.
谢谢。
Thank you.
-我能...？ -哦，不行。
-Can I...? -Oh, no.
你至少得让它保持那样几天。
You gotta leave that in for at least a couple days.
太有意思了。
Very funny.
搞什么鬼，汉克？
What the fuck, Hank?
我记不清昨晚发生什么了。
I can't remember what happened last night.
真让人震惊。
Shocker.
保罗说你来找他帮忙，然后开始喝酒，成了派对上的焦点，后来又对棒球满腹牢骚，所以...老样子了。
Paul said you came in asking for a favor, started drinking, were the life of the party, got old and bitter about baseball, so... The usual.
-我得走了。-什么？
-I have to go. -What?
你还没告诉我到底他妈的发生了什么事。
You still haven't told me what the fuck is going on.
事情变得不对劲。
Something fucked up is happening.
-我们报警吧。-不行，亲爱的。他们说不能叫警察。
-Let's call the cops. -No, baby. They said no cops.
行吗？
All right?
-我能搞定。-不！你不行。
-I can handle it. -No! You can't.
-这些人伤害猫咪。-你帮我看着他。
-These people hurt cats. -You watch him for me.
好的，我来照顾巴德。
Yeah, I'll take care of Bud.
-你要照顾好自己。-好的。
-You take care of yourself. -All right.
我晚点打给你？
I'll call you later?
保罗酒吧。保罗不在这儿。你老婆也不在。
Paul's Bar. Paul's not here. And neither is your wife.
--嘿，我是汉克。
--Hey, it's Hank.
昨晚我给你的那把钥匙？我需要拿回来。
The key I gave you last night? I need to get it.
你能打电话给我吗，呃...？
Can you call me at, uh...?
-汉克！-哦，该死！
-Hank! -Oh, shit!
小心！
Look out!
你这该死的白痴！
You fucking idiot!
给我注意点！你他妈的在干什么？
Pay attention! What the fuck are you doing?
对不起！
Sorry!
汉克。你跑什么？
Hank. Why you running?
-为什么跑？-冷静点。放轻松。
-For what? -Relax. Just relax.
不，不要，不行！
No, no, no!
汉克！
Hank!
快走！快走！
Move! Move!
哦，该死。
Ooh, fuck.
保罗酒吧。保罗不在。而且...也不在。
Paul's Bar. Paul's not here. And neither is...
再来杯啤酒？
Another beer?
当然记得。
Yeah, sure.
-喂？-我是汉克·汤普森。
-¿Hola? -It's Hank Thompson.
汉克。你想起什么了吗？
Hank. Did you remember something?
我知道钥匙在哪儿。
I know where the key is.
很好。它在哪儿？
Good. Where is it?
别让我猜来猜去。
Don't make me guess.
我现在就去拿。
I'm gonna go get it now.
我陪你一起去。
I'll go with you. To keep you company.
不，是和朋友约好的。不能带你去。
No, it's with a friend. I'm not taking you there.
哪个朋友？
Which friend?
啊，唐人街那个姑娘。
Ah, the chica in Chinatown.
- 什么？- 什么？
- What? - What?
什么？汉克，我告诉过你我们会怎么对付你在乎的人。
What? I told you what we'd do to the people you care about, Hank.
哦，不。
Oh, no.
天啊！天啊！
Oh, God! Oh, God!
911。请问您的紧急情况是什么？
911. What is your emergency?
喂？你能听到我说话吗？
Hello? Can you hear me?
你没回电话，我就好奇查了你，汉克。
When you didn't call back, I got curious, so then I looked you up, Hank.
我还在吹嘘自己打过正经比赛，结果你才是真正的天才球员。
There I was shining you about playing real ball, and you were an actual phenom.
老爷子肯定把你调教得特别棒。
Old man must have coached you real good.
十八岁。
Eighteen.
注定成为大联盟选秀的热门人选。
Set to be a top pick in the Major League draft.
然后你却搞砸了。
Then you messed it up.
你老爸一定很失望吧。
Your dad must have been pretty disappointed.
棒球生涯就此终结。
So much for baseball.
你本应从中吸取教训，但……看看我们现在。
You think you'd learn from that, but... ...here we are.
那是个近距离枪伤。
That...is a contact wound.
枪当时是这样抵着的。
The gun was like this.
有人闯入她的公寓埋伏，等她回来后就处决了她。
Somebody gained entry into her apartment, waited for her, then executed her.
不管你在搞什么勾当害死了这姑娘，我的职责就是确保不再有人遇害。
Whatever you're into got this girl killed, and it's my job to make sure nobody else gets murdered.
我需要一些信息。
I'mma need some information.
所以要么你告诉我...
So either you tell me...
明白了吗？
You got that?
听着，呃，别再盯着那些看了。
Look, uh, no more looking at those.
我们，呃...我们带你离开这儿。
Let's, uh... Let's get you outta here.
来吧。我们去喝杯咖啡。
Come on. Let's get a coffee.
行吗？
All right?
什么？
What?
你打算告诉我怎么回事吗？
You gonna tell me what's going on?
我需要你证明自己具备说话的能力。
I'd like evidence you possess the power of speech.
那是我妈妈。
It was my mom.
你妈妈怎么了？
Your mom what?
棒球。
Baseball.
妈妈是我的教练。
Mom was my coach.
说得好，妈妈。
Right on, Mom.
所以这些你招惹上的俄国人，帕维尔和阿列克谢？
So these Russians you're messed up with, Pavel and Aleksei?
他们实际上是替布莱顿海滩一个极恶之徒伊戈尔·多洛霍夫在本地的分支打掩护。
They front a local franchise for a truly evil fucker out in Brighton Beach, Igor Dolokhov.
还有那个红头发的，波多黎各人科罗拉多？
And the redhead, the Puerto Rican, Colorado?
他在他们的地盘上经营着几家夜店。
He runs a couple nightclubs over on their turf.
他就是杀害伊冯娜的凶手。
He's the one who killed Yvonne.
哼。他给你来了那套"手枪演说"？
Hm. He gave you that whole pistola speech?
没错。一字不差。
Yes. Exactly.
全是装腔作势。这混蛋嘴上厉害，真让他扣扳机就怂了。
It's all a front. Asshole talks big, but he ain't got the balls to pull the trigger.
处决式谋杀，那是德鲁克兄弟的惯用手法。
Now, execution-murder, that's the Drucker brothers' style.
利帕和舒穆利。哈西德派那帮人。
Lipa and Shmully. The Hasids.
等等，但是...她跟他们毫无瓜葛啊。
Wait, but... She had nothing to do with them.
哼，他们跟着俄国人找到你，又通过你盯上了她。
Well, they followed the Russians to you and you to her.
你逃跑了，还惹毛了他们。
And you ran, and you pissed them off.
别他妈招惹我们。
Don't fuck with us.
听着，这一团糟全是为了钱。
Look, this whole clusterfuck is all about money.
一笔数额惊人的现金。
An exotically huge amount of cash.
那把钥匙能打开它藏匿的任何地方。
And that key opens wherever it's hidden.
是拉斯偷的。不是你。
And Russ stole it. Not you.
汉克... ...这不是你的错。
Hank... ...it's not your fault.
我本该给你打电话的。
I should have called you.
她是对的。我为什么没听她的话？
She was right. Why didn't I listen to her?
我真是个混...
I'm such a fu...
钥匙在我工作的那家酒吧。
The key is at the bar where I work.
我交给老板保管，后来喝醉酒就忘了。
I gave it to my boss to hide it, and then I got drunk and I forgot.
好的？
OK?
好的。
OK.
给你。
Here you go.
好的。
OK.
这就是...这就是我来这儿的目的。
This... This is what I came here for.
嗯。
Mm.
-那我们现在怎么办？-等增援。
-So, what do we do now? -We wait for backup.
你喝过黑白配吗？
You ever had a black-and-white?
来吧，尝尝看。
Come on. Try it.
你错过了太多。
You're missing out.
嗯。那时候我还是个孩子，黑白电视的时代，这是这儿唯一值得一看的东西。
Mm. I was a kid, black-and-white, it was the only thing worth a shit down here.
我说的是真正的字母城。
I'm talking real Alphabet City.
可不是那种高档化矫情小餐馆的破玩意。
None of that gentrified chichi bistro bullshit.
我在 Avenue D 附近的里斯公屋区长大，就在那边。
I grew up in the projects right over there in Riis Houses off Avenue D.
在这里长大，也在这里工作。
Grew up down here, work down here.
但绝不会死在这个鬼地方。哼。
Ain't gonna fucking die down here. Mm-mm.
等这一切结束，我要去图卢姆。
When all of this is over, I'm going to Tulum.
沙滩泳池酒吧，可以游过去畅饮...我要坐在那儿，听涛声阵阵，畅想新生活。
Beaches, pool bar that you swim up to... I'mma sit there, listen to the waves, think about my new life.
唯一舍不得的就是这块曲奇了。
Only thing I'mma miss is this cookie.
嗯！
Mm!
后援已到。
Backup has arrived.
汉克，你这是要去哪儿？
Where you going, Hank?
这帽子不错。
Nice hat.
好了，我们开始吧。
All right, here we go.
好吧。所以呢？
OK. So?
里面情况怎么样？
How's it look in there?
店主和一个胖子正在吧台边吸可卡因。
The owner and some fat guy are doing coke at the bar.
那个胖家伙还要跟你老板混多久？
How much longer will the gordo ese hang out with your boss?
他有什么毛病？
What's his problem?
他以为你杀了他女人。
He thinks you killed his girl.
我告诉他你根本没胆子扣扳机。
I told him you don't have the balls to pull the trigger.
哈哈哈。
Ha-ha-ha.
-我们进去吧。-不，没必要进去。
-Let's go in. -No. We don't have to go in.
他会给我们送来的。
He's gonna bring it to us.
嗯。好吧。很好。
Hm. OK. Good.
你进去拿钥匙。
You go in and get the key.
-操你妈的混蛋！-嘿！少给我来这套！
-Fuck you, you motherfucker! -Hey! Knock that shit off!
汉克，你好像没抓住重点。
Hank, you seem to be missing the essence of the situation.
谁杀了你女人并不重要。
It doesn't matter who killed your girl.
重要的是你得采取行动，避免更多人送命。
What matters is that you do what you need to do so that nobody else gets killed.
你接下来要做的就是走进酒吧，拿到钥匙，然后带回来给我们。
So, what you're gonna do is go into the bar, you're gonna get the key, and bring it to us.
然后就结束了。噩梦到此为止。
And then that's it. It's over. Nightmare ends.
你只有一分钟时间，汉克。
You got one minute, Hank.
-不然我们就进去了。-好吧。
-Or we're comin' in. -All right.
不行，猫必须留在这里。
Nuh-uh. The cat stays here.
没事的，伙计。
It's OK, Bud.
然后她转向我，问我是否爱她。
And then she turns to me and asks me if I love her.
这是一个女士问她绅士朋友的合理问题。
That's a legit question for a lady to ask her gentleman friend.
怎么，你是在帮我还是耍我？
What, are you helping me or are you fucking with me?
听着，谈情说爱谁更在行，你还是我？
Listen, who the fuck knows more about romance, you or me?
-把这个给我 -什么？
-Give me this. -What?
-当然是我啊混蛋 -真的吗？
-Me, motherfucker. -Really?
是啊。我对自己的女性气质非常自信。
Yeah. I'm very in tune with my femininity.
- 这还用说！
- No shit!
让我进去！
Let me in!
麻烦来了。
Here comes trouble.
-哦哦，别给他可乐。-酒也不行。
-Uh-uh. No coke for him. -No booze either.
嘿，早上好啊，我的好朋友。
Hey, top o' the mornin' to you, my fine friend.
老兄，我需要我的钥匙。
I need my key, man.
什么钥匙？你在卖货吗？
A key of what? Are you selling weight?
-我的钥匙。现在就要。-你丢在哪了？
-My key. Right now. -Where did you lose it?
也许在失物招领抽屉里。
Maybe it's in the lost and found drawer.
我昨晚带给你的那把钥匙。
The key that I brought you last night.
在你搞坏台球桌呢绒之前还是之后？
Before or after you fucked up the felt on the pool table?
我给你的钥匙在哪儿？
Where is the key that I gave you?
你什么都没给我！
You didn't give me anything!
你只给我添了一堆麻烦。
All you gave me is a pain in the ass.
-什么？ -嘿，早上好啊。
-What? -Hey, good morning.
-再给我一分钟就好。 -安静点。
-I just need one more minute. -Quiet.
-嘿，你们在开派对吗？-这是...这是我家。
-Hey, you having a party? -It's... It's my place.
我们没伤害任何人。
We're not harming anybody.
我不必忍受眼前的一切。
I don't have to see everything I see.
-汉克，怎么回事？-汤普森先生正在协助调查。
-Hank, what's going on? -Mr. Thompson is helping with an investigation.
-昨晚他给了你钥匙？-听着，我觉得...告诉我们钥匙在哪儿，否则我们就搜你家。
-He gave you a key last night? -Listen, I think... Tell us where that key is, or we could search your place.
你有搜查令吗？操！
You got a fucking warrant?
这不关你的事，死胖子。
Not your problem, gordo cabrón.
别他妈叫我死胖子。
Don't call me fucking gordo cabrón.
告诉你的老板，你想要拿回属于你的东西。
Tell your boss you wanna reclaim your property.
- 对，对，但是我... -不，不，不。 -嘿，冷静点，阿姆特拉克。
- Yeah. Yeah, but I... -No, no, no. -Hey, cool it, Amtrak.
你他妈拿枪对着我？
You flash your fucking gun at me?
-嘿，阿姆特拉克！ -这混蛋根本不是警察！
-Hey, Amtrak! -This guy's no fucking cop!
-嘿，冷静点！-我认识警察！
-Hey, chill! -I know cops!
那根本他妈不是警察！
And that's no fucking cop!
靠！
Oh, fuck!
-美铁。美铁！-钥匙在哪？
-Amtrak. Amtrak! -Where is the key?
-别这样，老兄！-你有五秒钟。一...-你在干嘛？-问出答案。二...-我能搞定。-他他妈在说什么？
-No, come on, man! -You got five seconds. Uno... -What are you doing? -Getting answers. Dos... -I got it handled. -The fuck is he talking about?
-把枪放下。-三...-别数了，听着。-冷静点。
-Put the gun down. -Tres... - Stop counting, listen. - Calm down.
-四...-冷静下来！
-Cuatro... -Calm down!
-他妈的把枪放下！-求你了，老兄！求你了，求你了！
-Put the fucking gun down! -Please, man! Please, please!
五。
Cinco.
哦！天啊！
Oh! God!
真他妈谢谢你啊。
Fucking thank you.
这能糊弄得了谁？
That supposed to fool anyone?
就是个装样子的东西，懂了吗？
It's just supposed to look like a thing, all right?
混淆事实。
Confuse the issue.
哦。这看起来像个东西。
Oh. It looks like a thing.
汉克给了你一把钥匙。
Hank gave you a key.
我想要它。
I want it.
-等等，等等。-它在保险箱里。
-Wait, wait. -It's in the safe.
-保罗，我... -嗯。汉克。
-Paul, I... -Yeah. Hank.
钥匙在保险箱里。
The key is in the safe.
就放在你告诉我的地方。
It's where you told me to put it.
11-15-64。这锁有点挑剔，得轻轻晃动才行。
11-15-64. It's fussy. You gotta jiggle it.
-再给我报一遍数字。-11，15，64。
-Give me the numbers again. -11. 15. 64.
但我跟你说...你得...对，这确实挺难的，得掌握技巧才行。
But I'm telling... You gotta... Yeah, it's really tricky. You have to know how to do it.
-你搞不定的。-噢，见鬼！
-You can't do it. -Oh, fuck!
是啊，真他妈烦。
Yeah. Fuck.
好的。
OK.
你打开它然后出来。
You open it and then come out.
-好了吗？-明白了。
-All right? -Understood.
她这里很敏感。
She's very sensitive here.
只让我碰她。好了，宝贝。
Only lets me touch her. There you go, baby.
嘿，汉克，它来了。
Oh, hey. Hank, it's here.
我拿到了。噢，妈的！
I got it. Oh, shit!
-出去。-该死的膝盖。
-Out. -Fuckin' knees.
-啊！-枪！
-Aahh! -Gun!
混蛋！滚进我的酒吧来！
Motherfucker! Come into my bar!
你杀了我最好的兄弟！
You killed my best friend!
搞什么鬼，汉克？出什么事了老兄？
What the fuck, Hank? What's happening, man?
那些是什么人？他们把阿姆特拉克干掉了！
Who are those guys? They killed Amtrak!
他们竟然扫射我的酒吧！干死他们！
They shot up my bar! Fuck 'em!
趴下！
Get down!
他们朝我的宝贝蜥蜴开枪！
They shot at my fucking lizard!
-快走！-等警察来吧！
-Let's go! -Just wait for the cops!
别这样，保罗！保罗！住手！别这样！
No, Paul! Paul! Don't! Don't!
把钥匙从投递口扔进来，汉克。
Drop the key through the slot, Hank.
我他妈不知道那鬼东西在哪！
I don't know where the fucking thing is!
好吧，又不是世界末日。
OK, it's not the end of the world.
-先出来我们再... -我不出来。
-Just come out and we can... -I'm not coming out.
汉克，你必须出来。现在被抓的话，这些罪名全都会落到你头上。
You gotta come out, Hank. You get arrested now and all of this is gonna land on you.
- 我保证会这样。
- I'll make sure of it.
我们得走了。
We have to go.
汉克，我能帮你摆脱这个烂摊子。
I can get you out of this mess, Hank.
但我必须拿到那把钥匙。
But I have to have that key.
你被抓就完蛋了。
You get arrested, you're fucked.
嘿。嘿，杰森。杰森。
Hey. Hey, Jason. Jason.
我他妈宰了你！
I'll fucking cut you!
-退后！ -嘿，嘿，我是汉克。哈里。
-Back up! -Hey, hey, it's Hank. Harry.
-哈里。 -嘿，你拿了我的裤子，老兄。
-Harry. -Hey, you got my pants, man.
哦，天哪，我真的很喜欢这条裤子。
Oh, man, I really like these pants.
我知道，但我好像有东西落在口袋里了。
I know, but I think I left something in the pocket.
抱歉打扰了，伙计，我只是...哦。你说的是这个吗？
I'm sorry to disturb you, buddy, I just... Oh. You mean this?
是的，就是这个。谢了。裤子你留着吧。
Yes, I do. Thank you. You keep the pants.
哎呦，哈利，你可真是个好人。
Aw, man, you're all right, Harry.
你有一条新留言。
You have one new message.
亨利！天啊，你相信咱们的孩子们吗？
Henry! Oh my God, can you believe our boys?
他们居然在裸奔，大都会队和小熊队都拉胯了。
They're streaking, and the Mets and Cubs are shitting the bed.
就算没有超级巨星，他们也办得到。
They're gonna do it, even without their superstar.
真希望能有钱飞过去看比赛。
I wish I could afford to fly out.
我们可以一起看比赛。
We could watch the game together.
嘿，感觉好些了吗？
Hey, you feeling any better?
给我打电话。爱你。
Call me. Love you.
巨人队加油！
Go Giants!
啊！你这混蛋！
Ah! You fuck!
你他妈干嘛打我脑袋，白痴？
Why'd you hit me in the fucking 'ead, you twat?
你到底把我卷进了什么烂摊子？
What the fuck did you get me into?
-这他妈是什么鬼东西？ -坚持住！
-What is this shit? -Just hang on!
兄弟们。
Dudes.
他就是个该死的混蛋，对吧，汉克？
He's a fucking cunt, 'ey, Hank?
你也是个混蛋。
You're a cunt.
你为什么让我摊上这事？
Why did you stick me with this?
-干嘛，快给我。快给我！ -这能打开什么？
-What, gimme that. Gimme that! -What does it open?
-钱在哪？ -什么钱？
-Where is the money? -What money?
他们杀了伊冯，拉斯。
They killed Yvonne, Russ.
伙计...
Mate...
咱们去拿我的车吧，好吗？
Let's go get my wheels, yeah?
-你开吧。-不行。
-You drive. -No.
-你来开车。-不，我才不开。
-You're driving. -No, I'm not.
兄弟，我他妈视线都模糊了。
Mate, my vision's fucking blurred.
-我不开车。-啊。
-I don't drive. -Agh.
加州来的每个人都会开车。
Every cunt from California drives.
-我不会。-什么叫你不会？
-Not me. -What do you mean, not you?
去你的。
Fuck you.
你从没学过吗？
Did you never learn?
这就是他们把你赶出好莱坞的原因吗？
Is that why they kicked you out of Hollywood?
我又不是好莱坞的人。
I'm not from Hollywood.
这他妈是个比喻说法，汉克。
It's a fucking turn of phrase, Hank.
什么？是闲人乐队！
What? It's the Idles!
系好安全带。
Buckle your seat belt.
东村一家酒吧发生枪战的报道。
Reports of a shoot-out in an East Village bar.
据报道至少三人死亡。
At least three are reported dead.
警方正在搜寻该酒吧一名早先从警方拘留中逃脱的员工...
Police are searching for an employee of the bar who fled police custody earlier...
-你搞砸了，伙计。-我搞砸了？
-You fucked up, mate. -I fucked up?
去你的，拉斯！伊冯就是这样被处决的。
Fuck you, Russ! Yvonne was executed like this.
-嗷！-科罗拉多干掉了阿姆特拉克。
-Ow! -And Colorado killed Amtrak.
然后罗曼，她朝科罗拉多头部开了一枪，接着他们杀了保罗。
Then Roman, she shot Colorado in the head and then they killed Paul.
不是保罗。
Not Paul.
你他妈跟这些人搞什么鬼，哥们？
What the fuck are you doing with these people, man?
我会解释的。
I will explain.
但保证别再他妈的敲我脑袋了。
But promise to stop banging me in the fucking head.
-是吗？ -没事。
-Yeah? -Fine.
听着，老兄，很简单。
Look, mate, it's simple.
年轻时我认识了利帕和舒姆利，那两个希伯来人。
In my younger days I made an acquaintance with Lipa and Shmully, the Hebrews.
可以说我成了他们象征性的外邦人，就像换了个小挡位。
I became their token gentile, as it were, shifting a little gear.
什么装备？
What kind of gear?
该死的网球鞋啊，汉克。棒棒糖。
Fucking tennis shoes, Hank. Lollipops.
毒品，伙计。我就是干这个的。
Drugs, mate. That's what I do.
我在科罗拉多的俱乐部里出货。
I deal out of Colorado's clubs.
--滚开！
--Fuck off!
这些年来，我失去了莉帕和什穆利的踪迹，但最近他们又出现了，手里还掌握着数量惊人的比利时迷幻药。
So now, I lost track of Lipa and Shmully in the years, but recently they reappeared, having come into possession of an indecent fuckin' amount of Belgian ecstasy.
那玩意儿简直要命。
The fucking right bollocks, it was.
吃了会让你眼神涣散，下巴像海盗船一样晃个不停。
Makes your eyes go fucking that way and your jaw do that like a pirate ship.
但是……最丢脸的是，我最近刚被罗曼逮了个正着。
But...the shame of it was I happened to be recently busted by Roman.
欠她一个线报，不然就把我关进去。
Owed her a snitch on something or she'd lock me up.
所以听说 X 的事后，我就给她通风报信了。
So when I heard about the X, I filled her in.
但这贱人根本不想抓人。
But, filth that she is, she's not interested in making an arrest.
看明白了吧？因为她自己也欠这个该死的俄罗斯黑帮老大伊戈尔一屁股债。
See? Because she's in debt herself to this evil fucking Russian mob boss Igor.
-哦。-哇，你还好吗？
-Oh. -Whoa. You all right?
好吧。好吧。
All right. All right.
所以罗曼促成了这笔交易，在伊戈尔的地盘上通过科罗拉多的俱乐部销售 X 毒品。
So Roman brokered the deal to sell the X through Colorado's clubs on Igor's turf.
大家都能分一杯羹，但问题在于：
Everyone gets a cut, but here's the rub:
这些家伙没一个信得过对方管钱。
none of these fucks trust each other with the cash flow.
他们想最后来个大分账。
They wanna do a big split at the end.
所以老兄，他们需要个管账的。
And for that, my friend, they need a banker.
他们就放心让你管账？
And they trusted you to be their banker?
老子可不是什么混日子的废物，这是老子的饭碗。
I'm not some fucking wanker. I do this for a living.
我认识他们，有过节。
I know 'em. I've got history.
再说了，我他妈怕得要死。
Plus, also, I'm scared shitless of 'em.
他们知道我不会坑他们。
They know I won't fuck 'em over.
-可你确实上了他们。-但那他妈不是故意的！
-Except you did fuck them. -But not on fucking purpose!
你说你爸中风了。
You said your dad had a stroke.
对，他他妈的死了。
Yeah, he's fucking dead.
哦。
Oh.
哥们，听到这个我很难过。
Man, I'm sorry to hear that.
所以你当时不是想坑他们钱？
So you weren't trying to rip 'em off?
不是！我接到电话说我爸出事了，就立马回家了。
No! I got a call about Dad, I went home.
整个飞行途中我都魂不守舍。
That whole flight, I was mental.
到了伦敦发现我爸躺在重症监护室，半张脸肿得像布丁。
I get to London, Dad's in the fucking ICU, half his face is like a pudding.
哥们，操，我晕得不行。
Mate, fuck, I'm spinnin'.
然后那玩意儿真他妈上头了。
And it fucking hits me.
我谁都没说就溜了。
I dodged out without telling anyone.
我给语音信箱打了电话。
I call the answering service.
我收到上千条消息说要是拿不出钱就死定了
I've got a thousand messages saying how dead I am if I don't produce the money.
钱在哪？
So where is it?
还等什么？
What you waiting for?
拿着，派点用场
Here, hold this. Make yourself useful.
欢迎来到这该死的纳尼亚。
Welcome to fucking Narnia.
本打算在我走那天进行那笔大额分账。
Supposed to do the big split the day I left.
-有多少钱？ -切！
-How much is there? -Pff!
稍微超过……四百万。
Wee bit over... ...four million.
你把钥匙藏猫砂盆里了？
And you put the key in a litter box?
是啊！我哪能想到隔壁邻居会去翻那该死的猫屎啊？
Yeah. I didn't expect my next-door neighbor to go through the fucking cat shit, did I?
好吧，行。那我们打电话给罗曼。
OK. All right. OK. So we call Roman.
-不行，不能信她 -就告诉她钥匙在我们这儿
-No, we can't trust her. -We tell her we have it.
事情没那么简单。
It's more complicated than that.
复杂个屁！我只想回家。
Fuck complicated! I wanna go home.
我想见妈妈。我...哦，糟糕。妈妈。
I wanna see my mom. I... Oh, shit. Mom.
-电话。电话。-你想给你妈妈打电话吗？
-Phone. Phone. -You wanna phone your mum?
是啊。
Yeah.
别浪费我的通话时长。
Just don't use up my minutes.
是啊。顺便说一句，不客气。
Yeah. And you're welcome, by the way.
该死的...
Fucking...
嘿，妈妈。是我。
Hey, Mom. It's me.
他们过得很好。嘿，听我说。
Yeah, they're doing great. Hey, listen.
电视上可能会有新闻，或者警方可能会......妈。妈，你必须听我说。
There's going to be news on the TV maybe or maybe the police will... Mom. Mom, you gotta listen to me.
那不是真的，好吗？
It is not true, OK?
我没有做他们说的那些事。
I didn't do what they say.
-我现在没法解释。-挂电话。
-I can't explain right now. -Get off the phone.
我没事。我得走了。我爱你。
I'm OK. I have to go. I love you.
-快挂电话。-巨人队加油。
-Get off the phone. -Go Giants.
他们都以为我耍了他们，汉克。
They all think I fucked 'em, Hank.
我死定了，就算我带着钱出现。
I'm dead. Even if I show up with the money.
所以我要把钱全拿走然后逃走。
So I'm gonna take it all and run.
去拉瓜迪亚机场赶航班。
Catch a flight at LaGuardia.
那我怎么办？
So, what happens to me?
抱歉，伙计。你完蛋了。
Sorry, mate. You're fucked.
进来吧。求你了。
Get in 'ere. Please.
快进来！
Get in 'ere!
好的。行吧。这是你的手机。
OK. All right. Here's your phone.
好的。
All right.
罗斯，你他妈死哪去了？
Russ, the fuck have you been?
-是汉克。 -汉克？
-It's Hank. -Hank?
罗斯回来了。
Russ came back.
-钱在我这儿。 -有意思。
-And I have the money. -Interesting.
你说过能帮我脱身，具体怎么做？
Now, you said you could get me out of this. How?
需要大量打点费用。
It's gonna take a lot of payoffs.
-所以我需要资金 -嗯哼
-So I need the money. -Uh-huh.
-还有件事 -洗耳恭听
-And one other thing. -I'm listening.
替罪羊。
A fall guy.
除非你想蹲 20 年牢。
Unless you wanna do 20 to life.
——是啊，我也有个这样的。
--Yeah, I got one of those.
好了。这里是你要交钱的地方。
All right. Here's where you're gonna bring the money.
不，我来告诉你去哪。
No, I'll tell you where.
好吧。你有什么计划？
Fine. What's your plan?
首先，我要那只猫。
First, I want the cat.
- 我们去哪？- 拉瓜迪亚机场。
- Where are we goin'? - LaGuardia.
是！
Yes!
-你来开车。-我告诉你怎么走。
-You drive. -I'll tell you where to go.
-不，你...-你来开。
-No, y... -You're driving.
系好安全带。不会有事的。
Put your seat belt on. It'll be fine.
--小心！
--Watch out!
靠！
Oh, shit!
哦，好吧。我没事。行了吧？
Oh, yeah. I'm all right. All right?
-快让开，快让开。-闭嘴，我在开车。
-Pull off, pull off. -Shut up. I'm driving.
好了，就停这儿。
All right, stop here.
我们来早了。
We're early.
现在是 1010 WINS 体育广播的棒球节目时间。
It's time for 1010 WINS Sports with baseball.
大都会队今天在谢亚球场迎战勇士队。
The Mets are at Shea today with the Braves.
迈克·皮亚扎投出第三球。两人上垒。
Mike Piazza takes ball three. Two on.
该死的棒球。
Fuckin' baseball.
巨人队正在争夺外卡资格。
Giants are fightin' for the wild card.
我来聊聊英超，看你们有没有兴趣听。
I'll talk about the Premier League and see if you give a fuck.
与此同时，在科罗拉多，巨人队在第一局以一分领先。
Meanwhile, in Colorado, the Giants have taken a one-run lead in the first.
太他妈棒了。
Fuck yeah.
哇哦！威皮先生。
Ooh! Mr. Whippy.
-我们是在法拉盛草地公园吗？-嗯。
-Are we in Flushing Meadows? -Uh-huh.
我们得在航班起飞前接上巴德。
We have to pick up Bud before our flight.
巴迪？他在哪儿？
Buddy? Where is he?
喂。你把我的猫交给谁了？
Oi. Who'd you give my cat to?
我没把他交给任何人。
I didn't give him to anyone.
噢，你这该死的贱人！她会杀了我的！
Oh, you fucking cunt! She'll kill me!
-闭嘴。-不，滚开！
-Shut up. -No, fuck off!
-她会杀了我的！-没事的。
-She'll kill me! -It's gonna be OK.
她会先宰了我，再他妈宰了你！
She'll fucking kill me, then she'll fucking kill you!
- 不。搞什么鬼？见鬼！
- No. What the fuck? The fuck?
- 你必须相信我！
- You have to trust me!
-我凭什么要信你？-你...这个...棒球混蛋！
-Why would I ever do that? -You... Fucking... Mr. Baseball!
-啊！该死！-钱在哪？
-Aahh! Fuck! -Where's the money?
-我没有钱！-别相信她！
-I don't have the money! -Don't trust her!
关键是要你把钱带来。
The point was for you to bring the money.
我带了钥匙，拉斯会带你去拿钱！
I brought the key, and Russ will take you to the money!
-汉克！她杀了伊冯。-不。你得带我去找它。
-Hank! She killed Yvonne. -No. You'll take me to it.
-休想！-她会杀了你的！
-Not gonna happen! -She'll murder you!
-那就让她杀了我！-你们两个都给我上车。
-Then she'll murder me! -Both of you get in the car.
不！我他妈哪儿也不去！
No! I'm not going fucking anywhere!
-拉斯！拉斯！-去你妈的！操！
-Russ! Russ! -Fuck you! Fuck!
嘿，嘿，嘿！
Hey, hey, hey!
操。
Fuck.
哎哟！
Ow!
没错！混蛋们！就是这样，蠢货们，退后！
Yeah, that's right! Fuckers! That's it, fucktards, back up!
-老兄。老兄。
- Bud. Bud.
- 不许动！ - 不许动！
- Don't you move! - Don't you move!
去你的，给我停下。
Yeah, fuck you, stop.
把猫弄上车！
Get the cat in the car!
别动！后退！去你的！
Don't! Back up! Fuck you!
操！操，操蛋。
Fuck! Fuck, fuck.
- 滚开！ - 哦，操，操，操！
- Get out of the way! - Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck!
- 哦，见鬼！
- Oh, fuck!
操！
Fuck!
去你妈的，你这个该死的混蛋！
Fuck you, you fucking horrible cunt!
该死！
Shit!
操！
Fuck!
操！操！
Fuck! Fuck!
汉克，我觉得罗曼真的杀了伊冯娜！
Hank, I think Roman really did kill Yvonne!
别再说了！
Stop saying that!
听着！伊冯娜是被射中太阳穴而死的，对吧？
Listen! Yvonne was shot in the temple, right?
别再提这事了！
Stop talking about it!
罗曼当时也是这样对科罗拉多开枪的，对吧？
And Roman shot Colorado that exact same way, yeah?
拉斯，罗曼根本没理由这么做！
Russ, there's no reason for Roman to do it!
万一罗曼当时在伊冯家找钥匙呢？
What if Roman was at Yvonne's looking for the key?
伊冯进来了，事情就这样发生了。砰！
Yvonne came in and that was that. Bang!
一枪打中太阳穴。
One in the temple.
妈的见鬼！
Fuckin' 'ell!
开快点。再快点，拉斯！
Go faster. Faster, Russ!
哥们，我已经他妈的最快速度了！
Dude, I'm going as fast as I fucking can!
-我该往哪走？-往右。
-Where am I going? -Go right.
-往右！-明白了。
-Go right! -Got it.
--哇！操！
--Whoa! Fuck!
好的！
OK!
哦，见鬼！
Oh, shit a brick!
- 你要去哪儿？- 天杀的...
- Where you going? - Jesus fucking...
去你的！
Fuck you!
-开快点！ -操你妈的！
-Go faster! -Oh, you motherfuckers!
不！该死！
No! Fuck!
你这该死的猪！狗娘养的！别碰我的车！
You fucking pig fuck! You motherfuckers! Not my car!
-哦，该死！ -刹车！刹车！
-Oh, fuck! -Brake! Brake!
什...什么？
Wha...?
操。
Fuck.
好了，加速，加速，再加速！
All right, gas, gas, gas.
-真他妈搞笑，混蛋们！-快走，快走，快走。
-Very funny, cunts! -Go, go, go.
快走，快走，快走。
Go, go, go.
他们跑了。快！快！走，快走！
There they go. Come on! Come on! Let’s go, let’s go!
哇。伙计，我真的感觉不太舒服，老兄。
Whoa. Mate, I really don't feel too well, man.
拉斯。拉斯。嘿！
Russ. Russ. Hey!
拉斯。
Russ.
拉斯！拉斯！拉斯！
Russ! Russ! Russ!
我真的不该开车的。
I really don't think I should be driving.
该死的谢伊。
Fucking Shea.
我好像忘关炉子了。
I think I left the stove on.
♪ 兔子快跑... ♪
♪ Rabbit run... ♪
哦 是的
Oh. Yeah.
♪ 跑吧 ♪ 兔子，快跑... ♪
♪ Run ♪ Rabbit, run... ♪
-我得坐下歇会。-抱歉 实在抱歉。
-I need to sit down. -Sorry. Sorry.
等我们一上火车。
As soon as we get on the train.
本班列车为 7 号线法拉盛-缅街方向普通列车。
This is the Flushing-Main Street bound 7 local train.
- 左边，左边，左边！ - 动起来，动起来，动起来！
- Left, left, left! - Move, move, move!
那个巨人队的球迷说大都会队烂透了。你听到了吗？
That Giants fan said the Mets suck shit. You hear that?
就是那个巨人队的球迷！去你的！
That Giants fan right there! Fuck you!
对，去他妈的巨人队球迷！
Yeah, fuck that Giants fan!
请勿靠近正在关闭的车门。
Stand clear of the closing doors, please.
哇哦，老兄。
Wow. Buddy.
这是我的猫。
It's my cat.
下一站我们换乘列车，送你去急诊室，好吗？
At the next station, we switch trains and get you to an emergency room, all right?
汉克，你得照顾好巴德。
I need you to take care of Bud, Hank.
交给我吧，他现在没事了。
I got him. He's gonna be fine now.
你他妈最好说到做到。
Make sure you fucking do.
蠢货。
You twat.
好了，该走了。
All right. It's time to go.
请注意，车门即将关闭。
Stand clear of the closing doors, please.
饿死了。
Starving.
中餐还是汉堡。
Chinese or burgers.
我必须进食。
I have to eat.
♪ 咀嚼痛苦的面包 ♪ 啜饮暴力的酒浆 ♪ 甘愿被毒蛇征服 ♪ 为何违抗第一诫章？
♪ Unnu nyam the bread of sorrow ♪ Drink the wine of violence ♪ Allowed yourself to be conquered by the serpent ♪ Why you disobey the first commandment?
♪ 穿越幽谷无惧瘟疫 ♪ 上帝为我见证 ♪ 你终难逃这审判 ♪ 刽子手 ♪ 鲜血浸染你肩膀 ♪ 今日杀我明日难偿 ♪ 杀人狂
♪ Walk through the valley I fear no pestilence ♪ God is my witness ♪ You will never escape this judgment ♪ Murderer ♪ Blood is on your shoulder ♪ Kill I today you cannot kill I tomorrow ♪ Murderer
♪ 你的灵魂早已空洞 ♪ 夺取生命是何感受？
♪ Your insides must be hollow ♪ How does it feel to take a life?
♪ 你能躲过世人 却逃不过良知的审判 ♪ 吞下苦难的面包 ♪ 饮尽暴力的苦酒 ♪ 任由毒蛇将你征服
♪ You can hide from man but not your conscience ♪ Unnu nyam the bread of sorrow ♪ Drink the wine of violence ♪ Allowed yourself to be conquered by the serpent
♪ 为何违抗这第一条戒律？
♪ Why you disobey the first commandment?
♪ 即使穿越死亡幽谷也不惧瘟疫 ♪ 上帝是我的见证... ♪
♪ Walk through the valley I fear no pestilence ♪ God is my witness... ♪
- 嘿 小鬼
- 终点站到了
- Hey, kid. - End of the line.
♪ 救赎从何而来 ♪ 你永远逃不过这审判 ♪ 凶手 ♪ 鲜血沾染你双肩 ♪ 今日杀我 明日我必重生 ♪ 凶手 你的内心早已空洞
♪ From whence cometh help ♪ You will never escape this judgment ♪ Murderer ♪ Blood is on your shoulder ♪ Kill I today you cannot kill I tomorrow ♪ Murderer Your insides must be hollow
♪ 夺走生命是何感受... ♪
♪ How does it feel to take a life... ♪
♪ 像...一样摇撼你 ♪
♪ Rock you like a... ♪
汉克，你在吗？
You there, Hank?
我有话要对你说。
I have something to say to you.
加利福尼亚州帕特森市，汉诺威街 1115 号。
1115 Hanover Street, Patterson, California.
你想跑回家找妈妈吗？
You thinking of running back home to your mom?
再想想吧。
Think again.
你身边的人接连丧命。
People around you keep winding up dead.
你的高中同学。你的老板。你的女友。
Your high school buddy. Your boss. Your girl.
现在他们在中央车站找到拉斯了？
And now they found Russ at Grand Central?
看来你就是那个替罪羊了。
Guess that makes you the fall guy.
所有人都认为你是杀人犯。
Everybody thinks you're a killer.
你死定了。
You're as good as dead.
把钱带到隐士俱乐部。
You bring the money to the Hermitage Club.
布莱顿海滩。
Brighton Beach.
两小时之内。
In two hours.
也许我能避免牵连无辜。
Maybe I can stop the collateral damage.
汉克，你不可能永远逃下去。
You can't run forever, Hank.
操！
Fuck!
不，妈，你得离开房子。
No, Ma, you need to leave the house.
是的，我知道。我明白新闻里说的那些。
Yeah, I know. I know. I know what the news says.
是啊，我知道你明白这不是真的，但是妈妈，有人因我而丧命。
Yeah, I know you know it's not true, but, Mom, people got killed because of me.
这不是意外。
It's not an accident.
这和车祸不同，妈妈。
It is not like the car crash, Mom.
不，这...不，这完全一样，妈妈，因为...那都是我的错。
No, it's... No, it's exactly like that, Mom, because... ...that was my fault.
我杀了戴尔。
I killed Dale.
是的，妈妈，是我干的。
I did, Mom.
我杀了戴尔，当时满脑子只想着自己搞砸了膝盖，再也不能打棒球了。
I killed Dale, and all I thought about was how I fucked up my knee and I couldn't play baseball anymore.
我甚至根本没考虑过他。
I didn't even think about him.
我杀了戴尔。我一直在逃避这件事。
I killed Dale. I ran from it.
我从未正视过它。
I never owned it.
现在听我说，妈妈。
Now, listen to me, Mom.
我需要你离开这栋房子。
I need you to get out of the house.
你得去杰姬家。
You need to go to Jackie's.
在她家看比赛，妈妈！
Watch the game at her place, Mom!
求你了，求求你了。
Please, please.
你能答应我你会去吗？
Will you promise me that you're gonna go?
好的。我爱你，妈妈。
OK. All right. I love you, Mom.
巨人队加油。
Go Giants.
哥们儿。给你。
Bud. Here you go.
拉斯。
Russ.
不，我是邻居。汉克。
No, I'm the neighbor. Hank.
- 汉克？- 那个舞技超群的家伙。
- Hank? - The man with the moves.
对，就是他。
Yeah. Him.
拉斯去哪了？
Where's Russ?
死了。
Dead.
这倒是个意外转折。
Well, that's a twist.
但我能给你弄到钱。
But I can get you the money.
好的。
OK.
帮我个忙，汉克。
Do me a favor, Hank.
别让我们再追着你不放了，好吗？
Don't make us chase you again, OK?
不。我再也不会逃跑了。
No. I'm done running.
哇！
Whoa!
你这挥棒的力道可真够猛的。
Hell of a swing you got.
这让我想起了吉尔·霍奇斯。
It reminds me of Gil Hodges.
♪ CBS-FM 电台播放鲍勃·香农演绎的怀旧金曲 ♪...♪
♪ Bob Shannon plays your favorite oldies ♪ On CBS-FM... ♪
这是只可爱的猫。
It's a nice cat.
所以，汉克，你知道别来招惹我们，对吧？
So, Hank, you know not to mess with us, yes?
-知道。-很好。
-Yes. -Good.
我们的钱在哪儿你清楚吧，汉克？
You know where our money is, right, Hank?
它被锁住了。
It's locked up.
-拉斯有钥匙。-拉斯怎么了？
-Russ had a key. -What happened to Russ?
♪ 年初一切安好…… ♪
♪ You start the year all fine... ♪
我杀了他。
I killed him.
♪ 你是我最珍贵的情人…… ♪
♪ You're my little Valentine... ♪
你是怎么做到的？
How'd you do that?
我用棒球棒打了他。
I hit him with a baseball bat.
♪ 你笑起来就像复活节兔子... ♪
♪ You're the Easter bunny when you smile... ♪
所以你现在有他的钥匙了？
So you have his key now?
♪ 我的心在旋转... ♪
♪ My heart's in a whirl... ♪
不，罗曼拿着它。
No, Roman has it.
但只有我知道钱锁在哪里。
But I'm the only one who knows where the money's locked up.
我应该在一小时内和她见面。
I'm supposed to meet her in...an hour.
哦。
Oh.
这么急着送死，自己往陷阱里钻？
So eager to die that you'd walk into a trap?
我不去的话，她会杀了我妈。
She'll murder my mom if I don't.
钱在哪，汉克？
Where's the money, Hank?
♪ 如烟花般绚烂夺目 ♪ 沙滩上的你美得让人嫉妒... ♪
♪ Like a firecracker, I'm aglow ♪ When you're on the beach you steal the show... ♪
等你杀了罗曼后我再告诉你。
I'll tell you after you kill Roman.
嗯。
Mm.
♪ 一年中的每一天... ♪
♪ Every day ♪ Of the year... ♪
我们得做件善事，汉克。你知道什么是善事吗？
We have to do a mitzvah, Hank. You know what a mitzvah is?
就像特别的恩惠。
It's like a special favor.
我猜你不是犹太人吧？
I don't suppose you're Jewish, are you?
♪ 万圣节上的罗密欧与朱丽叶 ♪
♪ Romeo and Juliet on Halloween ♪
——哦！
--Oh!
哦。
Oh.
啊。
Ah.
我没有钥匙。
I don't have the key.
看起来不是。
It appears not.
- 我们没时间了。- 嗯。
- We are running out of time. - Mm.
嗯？
Eh?
好了，穿上衣服。
OK, get dressed.
吃吧，瘦小子。
Eat, skinny boy.
谢谢。
Thank you.
不吃东西她会不高兴的。
Eat or you're gonna upset her.
罗曼要你去见面的地方叫隐士居，是伊戈尔·多洛霍夫的私人俱乐部。
The place Roman wants you to meet her, Hermitage, it's Igor Dolokhov's supper club.
豪华大场子，跟俄罗斯版的拉斯维加斯似的。
Big fancy place. Like a Russian Vegas.
-全是布莱顿黑帮的人
-他们肯定得意忘形
-Crawling with Brighton mob. -They'll be overconfident.
他们不会发现我们来了。
They won't see us coming.
所以我们要这么做。
So we're doing this.
汉克。
Hank.
没有实力就别虚张声势。
If you can't bite, don't show your teeth.
-谢谢。-嗯。
-Thank you. -Mm.
-车！- 小心！
-Car! -Look out!
车！
Car!
- 这地方不错。- 就这儿。
- This is good. - Right here.
- 好的，兄弟。- 行。
- Yes, brother. - OK.
-你开过枪吗，汉克？-没有。
-You ever fired a gun, Hank? -No.
扣动扳机，是这世上最简单的事。
Pulling the trigger, easiest thing in the world.
-可悲的世界。-支离破碎的世界。
-Sad world. -Broken world.
我不会需要枪的。
I won't need a gun.
我们为什么要给你一把枪？
Why would we give you a gun?
让我看看你的手。
Show me your hands.
来吧。这儿，让我看看。
Come on. Here, lemme see 'em.
对，来吧。
Yeah, come on.
-他手还挺软的，是吧？-哦。
-He's got soft hands, huh? -Oh.
-放轻松。别着急。-停下，停下。待着。
- Easy. Take it easy. - Stop, stop. Stay.
-嘿！别动！-不行不行不行。快过来！
-Hey! Stay! -No, no, no. Come on!
我还以为要和你一起进去呢。
I thought I was going in with you.
我们为什么要拿你的生命冒险？嗯？
Why would we risk your life? Huh?
你得带我们去找那笔钱。明白吗？
We need you to take us to the money. Yes?
我必须进去。我得确认事情办妥了。
I have to go in. I have to know it's done.
我不进去，就休想让我带你们找到任何东西。
If I don't go in, I don't take you to anything.
你最好按我们说的去做。
Oh, you'll do what we tell you to do.
不然的话，我们不会动你妈妈，但会对她心爱的儿子做些让她生不如死的事。
If you don't, we're not gonna touch your mommy, but we'll do things to her beloved son that'll make her wish she was dead.
明白了吧。在这等着。别担心。
You understand that. Wait here. Don't worry.
一切都会好起来的。
All will be well.
该死的。
Goddamn it.
该死的。快点，快点，快点！
Fuck. Come on, come on, come on.
嘿，嘿。
Hey, hey.
喂，伙计们！伙计们！
Hey, guys! Guys!
你走错方向了！
You're going the wrong way!
伙计们！见鬼。
Guys! Shit.
混账东西！
Asshole!
该死的...
Fucking...
棒球先生
Mr. Baseball.
噢。
Ooh.
举起手来？
Stick 'em up?
哦。
Oh.
啤酒在这儿。还有花生糖。
Beer here. Cracker Jack.
要搭配薯条吗？
Do you want fries with that?
钥匙。马上交出来。
The key. Now.
-我没有。 -在哪？
-I don't have it. -Where is it?
我扔海里了。
I threw it in the ocean.
你他妈在耍我吗？
Are you fucking with me?
你永远不知道什么时候会出事。
You never know when something'll pop loose.
哦。
Oh.
啊！该死！
Aahh! Fuck!
你扣不下扳机的，汉克。
You can't pull that trigger, Hank.
他妈的闭嘴！
Shut the fuck up!
哦，刚才你差点把我唬住了。
Oh, you had me going for a minute.
你他妈根本不是个杀手。
You're not a fucking killer.
你说得对。我不是。
You're right. I'm not.
但那些家伙是。
But those guys are.
拿到钥匙。
Get the key.
钥匙不在她身上。
She doesn't have it.
-什么？ -快来吧。
-What? -Come on.
- 喂。嘿。 - 汉克。
- Oy. Hey. - Hank.
嘿，老兄。没事的。有我在。
Hey, Bud. It's OK. I got ya.
-这家伙。 -疯子。
-This guy. -Meshuggener.
好的，我们出发吧。该走了。
All right, come on. It's time to go.
-你要去哪儿？-我来开车。
-Where you going? -I'm gonna drive.
今天是安息日。
It's Shabbas.
我这位当拉比的兄弟。
My brother the rabbi.
-汉克，你来开车。-我不会开车。
-You drive, Hank. -I don't drive.
汉克，你之前耍我们玩的时候还挺有幽默感的。
Hank, we've had a sense of humor with you jerking us around.
但我们在哈西姆那儿已经够麻烦了，不能在安息日开车。
But we're in enough trouble with Hashem without driving on Shabbas.
开车吧，汉克。
Drive the car, Hank.
♪在科帕♪科帕卡巴纳♪哈瓦那以北最火热的地方...♪
♪ At the copa ♪ Copacabana ♪ The hottest spot north of Havana... ♪
-系好安全带。-开车吧，汉克。拜托了。
-Buckle your seat belts. -Drive the car, Hank. Please.
我们走。我们走。
Let's go. Let's go.
给你。
There you go.
-看路，汉克。-稳一点，慢一点。
- Eyes on the road, Hank. - Nice and slow.
那么，我现在会怎样？
So, what happens to me now?
对我们来说，明智的做法是除掉你。
Smart thing for us would be to get rid of you.
但那个男人深爱着他的母亲。
But the man loves his mommy.
他竭力对她尽孝，简直到了痴狂的地步。
He tries to do right by her and is truly meshuga.
我们怎能不对这样的男人心生喜爱呢？
How can we not feel fondness for a man like that?
你在期待什么呢，汉克？
What are you hopin' for, Hank?
- 我想回家。- 嗯。
- I wanna go home. - Mm.
你所经历的种种，或许家乡已无你容身之处。
Things you've seen and done, it may be home has no room for you.
什么？
What?
你想要的是问心无愧吗？
A clear conscience is what you want?
汉克，你觉得你能做到吗？
You think you can have that, Hank?
不知道。
I don't know.
我们可以给你 10 万美金。
What we could do, we could give you 100 grand.
-再加点。-也许再多加点，算是对你服务的酬劳。
-A little more. -Maybe a little more than 100 grand for services rendered.
有这么多钱，一个人能跑很远的路。
A man could run a long way on that much money.
再说，你本来也没想杀拉斯。
And besides, you didn't mean to kill Russ.
也许警察会相信你。对吧？
Maybe the police'll believe you. Right?
我的意思是，谁都看得出来你不是真正的杀手。
I mean, anyone can see you're not a real killer.
所以你这是在帮我积德？
So you're doin' me a mitzvah?
是我们帮你积德。
We're doin' you a mitzvah.
-打火机怎么了？ -哦，那是我的错。
-What happened to the lighter? -Oh, that's my fault.
- 兄弟，安息日呢 - 没事的。
- Brother, Shabbas. - It's all right.
汉克会帮我点火的。给。
Hank'll light it for me. Here.
现在你可得帮我个忙。
Now you do me a mitzvah.
扣扳机就行。
Just pull the trigger.
世上最简单的事。
Easiest thing in the world.
我不是故意偷的。我只是想借个火。
I didn't intend to steal it. I just needed a light.
大哥。
Brother.
我们为你的女儿感到遗憾。
We're sorry about your girl.
你从我们这儿逃走了，汉克。你让我们追着你跑。
You ran from us, Hank. You made us chase you.
你得知道别来招惹我们。
We had to let you know not to mess with us.
没错。只能怪你自己。
That's true. No one to blame but yourself.
可悲的世界。
Sad world.
破碎的世界。
Broken world.
你在干嘛？
What're you doing?
嘿，慢点。我们不想引人注目。
Hey, slow down. We don't wanna draw attention.
-轻点，汉克。慢点。 -嘿，嘿，嘿。
-Easy, Hank. Slow down. -Hey, hey, hey.
-汉克，慢点！ -嘿！你在干什么？汉克！
-Hank, slow down! -Hey! What're you doin'? Hank!
慢点！我们能解决这事的！
Slow down! We can sort this out!
-汉克，汉克！ -慢点，汉克！
-Hank, Hank! -Slow down, Hank!
-嘿！汉克！ -汉克！慢点！
-Hey! Hank! -Hank! Slow down!
住手！
Stop!
嘿。
Hey.
你没事吧？你没事的。
You all right? You're all right.
好的。
OK.
我们真不该让那外族人开车。
We shouldn't have let the goy drive.
所以，我那几个哥们儿说服我别坐地铁。
So, my mates convinced me to skip the underground.
谁能想到他妈的在出租车里也能出车祸？
Never think you'll get in an accident in a fucking taxi, do ya?
说真的，谁系安全带啊？也就他妈的老太太们吧？
I mean, who wears a seat belt, fucking grannies?
我整个脸直接撞上了有机玻璃防护罩，-对吧？-还有人受伤吗？
Went face-fucking-first into the plexiglass shield, -didn't I? -Anyone else hurt?
没有，就我一个。不过我告诉你，我一定要把那该死的出租车公司告到倾家荡产。嗯？
No, just me. Tell you what, I'm suing the shit out of that fucking cab company, though. 'Ey?
-有行李吗，迈纳先生？-就一件。
-Bags, Mr. Miner? -Just one.
喂。
Oi.
挺沉的。
Heavy.
是啊，带些线缆、迷你音箱之类的玩意儿。
Yeah, well, cables, mini amp and shit.
在那边接了几场演出。
Playing some gigs down there.
-旅途愉快。-谢谢。
-Have a good trip. -Thank you.
下一个。
Next.
喂，是我，妈。
Hey, it's me, Ma.
嗯，我没事。
Yeah, I'm OK.
你可以回家了，现在安全了。
You can go home. It's safe now.
听我说。
Listen to me.
妈妈，我得离开一阵子。
Mama, I gotta go away for a while.
不过一切都会好起来的。
But it's gonna be OK.
不，我不能回家。
No, I can't come home.
我需要先照顾好自己一段时间。
I just need to take care of myself for a while.
过几天你会收到一个包裹。
You're gonna get a package in the next few days.
那是我全部家当的一半。
It's half of everything I have in the world.
妈 我现在得挂了 但我非常爱你。
Hey, Mom, I gotta go right now, but I love you so much.
你可以在家观看决胜局。
You can watch the tie-breaker at home.
巨人队加油。
Go Giants.
-谢谢。-非常感谢。
-Thank you. -Thank you so much.
棒球怎么样？
Baseball OK?
啤酒？还是玛格丽特？
Beer? Margarita?
苏打水吧。
Club soda.
好可爱的猫。
Nice cat.
你把他照顾得很好吗？
You take good care of him?
我在努力。
I'm trying.
- 他爱咬人。 - 哦。
-He's a biter. -Oh.
邦兹，这位可能根本没轮到击球的选手，不仅将上场击球，还可能是追平比分的关键跑垒员...就靠你了，伙计。
Bonds, who might not have even batted this inning, not only will bat but he is the possible tying run... Just you and me, Bud.
...尽管巨人队在这局开始时落后 5 分。
...even though a 5-run deficit faced the Giants when the inning started.
巴里·邦兹对阵穆赫兰。
So Barry Bonds against Mulholland.
邦兹在 46 次打席中击出六支本垒打。
Six homeruns for Bonds in those 46 at-bats.
邦兹连续第二次满垒上场击球。投球来了。
Bonds batting with the bases loaded for the second straight time. And here comes the pitch.
♪ 安迪会冒雨骑车穿过城镇 ♪ 为你送来糖果 ♪ 约翰会买下礼服 ♪ 让你穿着去毕业舞会 ♪ 与天文学家汤姆共舞 ♪ 他会以你的名字为星辰命名
♪ Andy would bicycle across town ♪ In the rain to bring you candy ♪ And John would buy the gown ♪ For you to wear to the prom ♪ With Tom the astronomer ♪ Who'd name a star for you
♪ 但我是最幸运的男孩 ♪ 在下东区的街头...
♪ But I'm the luckiest guy ♪ On the Lower East Side... ♪
操！
Fuck!
♪ 因为我拥有车轮 ♪ 而你想兜风漫游
♪ 'Cause I've got wheels ♪ And you wanna go for a ride
♪ 哈里是你想嫁的人 ♪ 却与克里斯放学拥吻 ♪ 噢我多傻 毋庸置疑 ♪ 但当阳光洒落大地 ♪ 唯有阳光普照之时
♪ Harry is the one I think you'll marry ♪ But it's Chris that you kissed ♪ After school ♪ Well, I'm a fool, there's no doubt ♪ But when the sun comes out ♪ And only when the sun comes out
♪ 我是最幸运的男孩 ♪ 在下东区的街角 ♪ 因为我拥有车轮 ♪ 而你想与我乘风奔跑
♪ I'm the luckiest guy ♪ On the Lower East Side ♪ 'Cause I've got wheels ♪ And you wanna go for a ride
♪ 你想不想一起去兜风... ♪
♪ And you wanna go for a ride... ♪
♪ 跑吧 ♪ 兔子，快跑
♪ Run ♪ Rabbit, run
♪ 为附带伤害让路 ♪ 当我无聊时 ♪ 挑逗野兽臂上的痂 ♪ 直到它被摧毁当我无聊时 ♪ 哦，有太多事可做 ♪ 或不做当我无聊时
♪ Make way for collateral damage ♪ When I'm bored ♪ Pick the scab on the arm of the beast ♪ Till it's ravaged when I'm bored ♪ Oh, so many things to do ♪ Or not do when I'm bored
♪ 随我心意执掌缰绳 ♪ 直到忧郁当我无聊时
♪ Takes the reins as I please myself ♪ Till I'm blue when I am bored
♪ 四面墙让我窒息 ♪ 百无聊赖时血脉偾张 ♪ 坐雪橇 乘游艇 ♪ 烦闷时肆意发泄暴力 ♪ 有股躁动正从 ♪ 我后颈窜起
♪ The walls feel small ♪ My veins are pulling when I am bored ♪ Do the luge, take a cruise ♪ Assault and batter when I am bored ♪ Something's coming from ♪ The back of my neck
♪ 它知我空虚至极 ♪ 逃吧 ♪ 兔子 快逃
♪ And it knows I'm bored ♪ Run ♪ Rabbit, run
♪ 如蟒蛇般缠上我身 ♪ 似牙痛般压迫难忍 ♪ 像你父亲般慢条斯理折磨你 ♪ 让你如越狱般仓皇逃遁 ♪ 逃吧 ♪ 兔子 快逃 ♪ 兔子 快逃
♪ Come to me like a boa snake ♪ Pressing on me like a toothache ♪ Beat you slow like your padre ♪ Got you running like a jailbreak ♪ Run ♪ Rabbit, run ♪ Rabbit, run
♪ 过来对我说 ♪ 我是忠实的奴仆 ♪ 过来帮帮我 ♪ 偿清我的债务
♪ Come over and tell me ♪ I'm a faithful serviette ♪ Come over and help me ♪ Pay my debts
♪ 呜！
♪ Woo!
♪ 如蟒蛇般向我缠绕而来 ♪ 如牙痛般对我紧追不舍 ♪ 像你父亲那样慢慢击垮你 ♪ 让你像越狱般仓皇逃窜
♪ Come to me like a boa snake ♪ Pressing on me like a toothache ♪ Beat you slow like your padre ♪ Got you running like a jailbreak
♪ 快跑
♪ Run
♪ 逃吧 兔子 ♪ 逃吧 兔子
♪ Rabbit, run ♪ Rabbit, run